

Marc Pifarré

Skilled culinary professional with broad experience in French, Italian and Spanish cuisine, a la carte, buffet and fine dining experiences.

Artistic menu design utilizing seasonal products. Exhibit a unique blend of creative flair and passion for food, strong business sense and oriented to the formation and team management.

CHEF / CULINARY ADVISOR

Professional Experience

-1

Bergen Ave, 821 Jersey City, NJ

+1 (646) 975-7645

Marcpj81@gmail.com

Barcelona, Spain October 22, 1981

Residence and Work Permit :

Visa Permanent Resident

CULINARY ACUMEN

- *Events
- *Fine Dining
- *A La Carte
- *Banquet Service
- *Creative Menu

Development

- *Management
- *Price Structuring & Cost
- *Special Event Planning
- *Safety & Sanitation
- *Quality Control
- *Profit Enhancement
- *Inventary & Purchasing

Madrid, Spain • March 2014 – September 2018 • Bonduelle • Corporate Chef

- Culinary advisor in restaurants in northern Spain
- Help in the management of restaurants, product demonstrations, driving and team building.
- Creation of new products and service with high results, Marketing Support.

Seoul, South Korea • June 2011 – January 2014 • El Olivo Group • Executive Chef

- Kitchen Operations Manager (3 restaurants)
- Recruit, train and supervise teams. Oversee all kitchen operations, including quality, plating and sanitation.
- Scope of responsibility includes purchasing, inventory control, menu research and development.

San Sebastián, Spain • April 2007 – June 2011 • Hotel Jaizkibel • Chef

- Kitchen Operations Manager
- Management team of cooks. Develop menu. Purchase Management.
- Kitchen Accounting

Education

2006 - 2007 • Postgraduate Management of Hostelry • ESHOB Barcelona

 Finance, taxation, accommodation, recruitment and training of employees, personnel management, team leadership, marketing, statistical procedures, management mechanisms.

1999 - 2002 • Superior Culinary Diploma • HOFMANN Culinary School Barcelona

 Accounting, French, Dietetics, Oenology, Customer Service, Human Resources, Gastronomic culture.

Compétences

Languages

English Intermediate Spanish Native speaker

Computer Knowledge

Word, Excel, Internet, Access, PowerPoint